Milton R. Konvitz Additional Papers /4085
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Horace Kallen & Milton Konvitz Publications (Box 23)
  - Horace Kallen (NOTE: this is the bottom box) (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Horace Kallen Interviews (Note: top box) (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - "Mexicano De Derecho Comparado" - Boletin Vol. VII No. 19 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - "Mexicano de Derecho Comparado" - Boletin Vol. VII No. 19 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - "Mexicano de Derecho Comparado" - Vol. VII No. 19 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Syracuse Journal of International Law and Commerce Spring 1975 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - American Jewish History December 1980 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - "Is the Constitution Color-Blind?" - Konvitz (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Syracuse Journal of International Law and Commerce - Spring 1975 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - American Jewish History December 1980 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - American Jewish History December 1980 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Subject Files & Publications, Correspondence, Current (Box 24)
  - Civil Liberties in America (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - "State Civil Rights Agencies: The Unfulfilled Promise" (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Education Articles (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Catholicism Articles (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - The American Philosophical Association Vol. 60 and 61 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - General Political/Legal Thought Articles (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Federal Issues/US Congressional Laws (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - "We the People" Newsletters (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - US Senate and US House of Representatives Reports (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Supreme Court: General (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Supreme Court: Rehnquist (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Court Rulings and Their Effects (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - New York State Cases and Supplements (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Federal Supplement and Cases (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Ethnicity and the Law (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Law Journals (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - American Foreign Policy (Minus Europe) (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - American Foreign Policy: Europe (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - American Foreign Policy: Israel/Palestine (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - American Foreign Policy: Terrorism (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - "American Foreign Policy" Newsletters (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - "Near East Report" - Various Issues from 3/3/1986-11/9/1987 (Chronologically) (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - "Boycott Report" - January, February, August, September, and October 1986 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Judaism (1 of 4) (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Judaism (2 of 4) (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Judaism (3 of 4) (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Judaism (4 of 4) (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - CLSA Reports (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - National Ramah Commission: Board Meeting August 9/10, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - New York State/Tompkins County (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Cornell University (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Milton Konvitz Letters (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Essay from Eugene Kamenka to Milton Konvitz (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - TVA Financial Statements 1986 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - "The New Yorker" (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - ACADEME July-August 1986 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - ACLU: Women's Rights Project (Box 24, Folder 39)
- ILR, CURW, Law School (Box 25)
  - Misc. Staff - ILR (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - ILR Report (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - State Colleges - Cornell (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Senate of State University (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Law School - Assistant Deans (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Law - General (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Law School - Misc. Faculty (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Law School - Minutes of Meetings (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Cornel Law Review (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Hillel Foundation - Morris Goldfarb (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Re Books of Milton Konvitz, Correspondence & Publications (Box 26)
  - Freedom House (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Government Printing Office (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Publishers: Harcourt, Brace & Co., Inc. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Harper & Brothers (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Heath, DC & Co. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Houghton Mifflin Co. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Publishers: Irwin (Richard D.), Inc. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Alfred A. Knopf, Inc. (Dr. Robert W. Shugg) (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Liberal Arts Press (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - MacMillan Company (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Nelson & Sons, Thomas (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - New American Library of World Literature, Inc. (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - WW Norton & Co., Inc. (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Prentice-Hall, Inc. (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Oxford University Press (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Penguin Books, Inc. (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Princeton University Press (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Rand McNally & Co. (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Random House, Inc. (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Regnery (Henry) Co. (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Charles Scribner's Sons (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - South-Western Publishing Co. (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Van Nostrand Co., Inc. (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Viking Press, Inc. (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - West Publishing Co. (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Meridian Books, Inc. - World Publishing Co. (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Publishers (A-K) (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Publishers (L-Z) (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Supreme Court of the United States (October 1968) (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - US Senate Committee on Commerce (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Computerization of Government Files: What Impact on the Individual? (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Cornell University ILR 1969-70: 16 mm Films (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - 91st Congress, Session 1: HR 11009 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Ad Hoc Committee to Defend the Right to Teach (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Civil Liberties (General) (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Fortas Articles (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Civil Unrest Articles (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Race Articles (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Federal Supplement - Articles (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Miscellaneous Articles (Box 26, Folder 41)
- ILR, CURW, Law School (Box 27)
  - Annual Reports - Mrk (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Dept. of Collective Bargaining (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Dept. of Collective Bargaining - Conference on Curriculum (Oct. 19-20, 1970) (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - American Labor Union Guidebook - Committee (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Committee on International Activities (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Extension Division - ILR (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Library - ILR (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - ORI - ILR (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Minutes of Faculty Meetings - ILR (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Faculty - ILR (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Dean - Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Assistant Dean Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Calvert - Herson (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Staff - ILR (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Publications (civil right) (Box 28)
  - Georgetown University (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Douglas M. McCabe (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - "The Federal Sector's Labor Relations Environment and Civil Service Reform" - McCabe (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Labor Unions and Mediation (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Business and Society (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Research Conferences (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Society of Professionals in Dispute Resolution (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Railroad Industry (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - "The Crew Consist Issue in the Railroad Industry" - McCabe (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Civil Rights and Liberties (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - "Responsibilities of Multinational Corporations to Society" - Vol II (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - "Concepts" - Summer 1981 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - "Mediation and Labor-Management Relations in the Federal Government" - McCabe (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - "The Federal Civil Rights Enforcement Effort - A Reassessment" - January 1973 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - "A Generation Deprived" (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Domestic Council Committee on Illegal Aliens - December 1976 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Report to the Congress by the Comptroller General of the United States - September 28, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Reports by the US Commission on Civil Rights (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Israel Law Review: Vol. 2 and 5 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Israel Law Review Vol. 6 No. 1 and 2 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Israel Law Review Vol. 6 No. 3 and 4 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Israel Law Review Vol. 7 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Israel Law Review Vol. 8 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Israel Law Review Vol. 9 and 10 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Subject Files (religion) (Box 29)
  - Sub-Files Religion (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Religion Part 2 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Poverty and Religion (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Church and State (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Religion Part 3 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Religion Part 4 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Religion Definition (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Religion Definition Cases (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Religion and Civil Liberties (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Religion and the State (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Religion and the State (Cont.) (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Subject Files, Publications, Correspondence & Current (Box 30)
  - Judaism (1 of 3) (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Judaism (2 of 3) (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Judaism (3 of 3) (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Race Relations (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Civil Rights/Liberties (1 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Civil Rights/Liberties (2 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Labor and Labor-Related (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Global Warming (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Catholicism (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Prayer (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Pornography (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Court Cases and Decisions (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Bork (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - US Constitution (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - US Politics (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - International Affairs: General (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - International Affairs: Human Rights and Aid (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - International Affairs: Europe (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Council of Europe (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Near East Report (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - American Foreign Policy Newsletter (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Foreign Policy-related (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Tompkins County (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Cornell University (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Milton Konvitz Mail (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - American Jewish Congress (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - "Measure" No. 67 and 69 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Recent Book Lists (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - The Journal of Law and Religion (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous Journals (Box 30, Folder 30)
- Milton Konvitz Publications (articles, etc.) (Box 31)
  - M.R. Konvitz Publications: Undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications: 1938 and Before (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications: 1940 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications: 1941 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications: 1942 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications: 1943 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications: 1944 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications: 1945 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications: 1946 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications: 1947 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications: 1948 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications: 1949 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications: 1950 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications: 1951 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications: 1952 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications: 1953 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications: 1954 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications: 1955 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications: 1956 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications: 1957 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications: 1958 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications: 1959 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications: 1960 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications: 1961 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications: 1962 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Address: Dedication Ceremonies - October 2, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 26)
- Milton Konvitz Publications (articles & books) (Box 32)
  - Judaism (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Syracuse Journal of International Law and Commerce (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - "Ameryka" (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Books: Aspects of Liberty (Cushman Festschrift and Robert E. Cushman) (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Funk and Wagmall's Encyclopedia (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - H.M. Kallen (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Civil Rights in Immigration - Book (MRK) (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Book: Constitutional Law (Rand McNally and Co.) (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Book: Freedom House 1964-65 (Folder 1) (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Books: Freedom House 1964-65 (Folder 2) (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Books: Columbia University Press - "Constitution and Civil Rights" (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Book: Pragmatism - Meridian Books, Inc. etc. (Projected: October 1958) (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Books: A Century of Civil Rights - Columbia University Press (Published 1961) (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Book: The Twentieth Century Views - Ralph Waldo Emerson (Prentice-Hall) (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Books: Reviews by Milton R. Konvitz (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Books: Writings, misc. (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Cornell University Press (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - The Viking Press (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - "The Role of Trade Union Leaders in the Development of Trade Unionism in an Under-Developed Area; the British Caribbean" (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Books & Correspondence Files (Cornell University & Committees, others) (Box 33)
  - The National Curriculum Research Institute (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Library Committee - Statler Club (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Encyclopedia Judaica: Requested Articles (Folder 1) (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - The Hebrew Culture Foundation, Inc. (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Encyclopedia Judaica (Labor) (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Encyclopedia Judaica: Manuscripts Received (Folder 2) (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - FCSPE (1965-66) (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - FCSPE (Novarr File #4 old) (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - FCSPE - Minutes and Rosters (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Scheduling Public Events Committee - IRM Personal (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - FCSPE (Documents and Policy) (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - FCSPE - Calendars (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - FCSPE - SCARB (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Law School Graduate Students - Special Committee Member (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Graduate Students: Misc. (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Friess, Alan Irwin (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Graduate Student: Kuboniwa, Kazuko (1962) (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Muraskin, Matthew (Ph.D. Candidate) (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Fisher, Linda Joyce (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Edwin F. Beal (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Boquiren, Felixberto (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Graduate Student: Bradburd, Arnold (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Graduate Students: Cornwall, Harry (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Graduate Students: Cullen, Donald Eugene (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Graduate Students: Demeo, Esther (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Graduate Students: Dye, Joseph Taylor (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Graduate Student (Law): Dwivedi, Devendra N. (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Gensler, Peter Alfred (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Graduate Students: Ghent, Donald Frank (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Emery Hey (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Graduate Students: Lim, George (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Graduate Students: Richard M. Lyon (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Mascola, Francis X. (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - OLES, Carl John (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Graduate Students: Risley, Robert F. (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Assistant: Ross, Harold (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Roth, William (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Sanuy, Gistau Francisco (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Jacob Seidenberg (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Graduate Student: Scobel, Donald (Box 33, Folder 40)
- Books & Correspondence Files (Cornell University & Committees, others) (Box 34)
  - Stuart, D. Dean (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Students: Weinberg, Herbert (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Wolfe, Terence (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Graduate School: Minutes of Meetings, Legislation, Memos, etc. (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - University: Westin + Konvitz (Joint Project) (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Committee: Joint Faculty-Student Relations (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Fraternity Discrimination (Cornell) (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Admissions: African Studies Inquiries (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Committee: International Activities Committee (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - International Studies and International Affairs: African Studies, etc. (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Committee on African Studies (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - University: Mimeographed Announcements (1960) (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Committee: Subcommittee of Committee on University Lectures (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Council: Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Council - Minutes of Meetings (1965) (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Committee: Quality of Undergraduate Instruction (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Student Exchange Program (Atlanta Project) (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Committee (University): Committee on Academic Freedom (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - University: Minutes - University Faculty (1960) (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - University: University Library (Reichmann, Shepard, McCarthy, et al.) (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Committees and Clubs (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Ascoli, Max (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Bicentennial - 1975 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - B'NAI B'RITH - Women's Bicentennial Committee (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Cole, David L. (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Commentary (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - B.H. Blackwell, LTD. (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Publishers: Inquiries for American Ideals Course (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - American Book Company (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Appleton-Century-Crofts Co., Inc. (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Beacon Press (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Bobbs-Merrill Co., Inc. (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Cambridge University Press (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Harvard University Press (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - University of Chicago Press (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Collier Books (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Columbia University Press (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Cornell Campus Store (Book Orders) (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Dennis and Co., Inc. (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Doubleday and Co. (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - E.P. Dutton and Co. (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Foundation Press, Inc. (The) (Box 34, Folder 42)
- Publications (civil rights) (Box 35)
  - School Desegregation in Ten Communities (June 1973) (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - School Desegregation in Ten Communities (June 1973) (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Challenges of Our Time: Prejudice and Discrimination (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - The Federal Fair Housing Enforcement Effort (March 1979) (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Desegregation of the Nation's Public Schools: A Status Report (February 1979) (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Desegregation of the Nation's Public Schools: A Status Report (February 1979) (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Toward Fair Employment and the EEOC (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Twenty Years After Brown: Equality of Educational Opportunity (Draft) (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - The Federal Civil Rights Enforcement Effort - 1977 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Civil Rights and Liberties Handbook: Pleadings and Practice (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Civil Rights and Liberties Handbook: Pleadings and Practice (1963) (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - National Foundation for Jewish Culture: Reports on the Jewish Cultural Field (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Civil Rights and Liberties Handbook: Pleadings and Practice (1963) (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Fair Textbooks: A Resource Guide (December 1979) (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - 6th Annual Report: Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - 7th Annual Report: Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Cairo, Illinois: Racism at Floodtide (October 1973) (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Promise v. Performance: A Study of Equal Employment Opportunity in the Nation's Electric and Gas Utilities (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Para Los Ninos - For the Children (October 1974) (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Labor Union Control of Job Training (Box 35, Folder 20)
- Merrill Trust; Cornell University Course Documents; Committee Documents (Box 36)
  - Merrill Trust - 1972 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Merrill Trust - 1971 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Merrill Trust - 1970 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Merrill Trust - 1969 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Merrill Trust - 1968 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Merrill Trust - 1967 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Touro College (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Development of American Ideals - ILR 408, 409 - Fall 1972, Spring 1973 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Development of American Ideals - ILR 408, 409 - Fall 1971, Spring 1972 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Development of American Ideals - ILR 408, 409 - Fall 1970, Spring 1971 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Development of American Ideals - ILR 408, 409 - Fall 1969, Spring 1970 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Development of American Ideals - ILR 408, 409 - Fall 1968, Spring 1969 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Development of American Ideals - ILR 408, 409 - Fall 1967, Spring 1968 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Development of American Ideals - ILR 408, 409 - Fall 1966, Spring 1967 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Development of American Ideals - ILR 408, 409 - Fall 1965, Spring 1966 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Development of American Ideals - ILR 408, 409 - Fall 1964, Spring 1965 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Development of American Ideals - ILR 408, 409 - Fall 1963, Spring 1964 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Development of American Ideals - ILR 408, 409 - Fall 1962, Spring 1963 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Development of American Ideals - ILR 290, 291 - Fall 1961, Spring 1962 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Development of American Ideals - ILR 290, 291 - Fall 1960, Spring 1961 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Fall 1958 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Spring 1958 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Fall 1957 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Spring 1957 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Fall 1956 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Spring 1956 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Spring 1951 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- Cornell University Correspondence (Box 37)
  - Cornell - Black Studies (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Cornell - Judaic Studies Professor (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Jewish Studies (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Cornell - Chairman, Semitic Department (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Yiddish (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - University - International Student Office (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Membership of Faculty (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Oral History Project (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Council - Correspondence (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Academic Freedom (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - University Faculty - Minutes of Meetings (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - President's Office (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Committees and Clubs - Miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - MEMO - Dean of Faculty (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - MEMO - Provost (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Cornell University Course Documents; Committee Documents (Box 38)
  - ILR 600 - Collective Bargaining: Labor Relations Law and Legislation (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - 500-Level Labor Relations Law Offering (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - ILR 290-91 - American Ideals Plans for 1953-54 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - ILR 72 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - ILR 69 - Patterns of Thought in Industrial and Labor Relations (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - ILR 651 - Theories of Industrial and Labor Relations (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Constitutional Litigation (Law School) (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - New Course: Constitutional Liberties (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Law School Course - Jurisprudence (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - ILR 300 - Labor Relations Law and Litigation Examinations (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - ILR 293 - Survey of Industrial and Labor Relations Examinations (Summer 1950) (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - ILR 72 - Civil Rights in Industrial and Labor Relations Examinations (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - ILR 69: Patterns of Thought Examinations (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - ILR 42 - Labor History Examinations (Summer 1949) (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - ILR 393 - Elements of Law Examinations (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - ILR 60 - Collective Bargaining Reading Assignments (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Margulies, William (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Law 500 - Civil Rights (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Law 502 - Constitutional Liberties Litigation (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Law 315 - Law and Poverty (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Seminar Vo. - 6 Year Ph.D. (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - ILR 309 - American Ideals (General) (Box 38, Folder 22)